As Prophet T.B. Joshua ministers prayer in the mighty name of Jesus Christ,
all the works of satan in the lives of the people are destroyed,
bringing them out of the kingdom of darkness and into the kingdom of light.
As the man of God prays for this woman,
she falls to the ground as the evil spirit inside her begins to manifest.
Let us hear what it has to say.
I am a snake from the father's side.
Yes.
No peace. She thinks she wants to be married. For what?
There's no peace. The husband has another woman - for two years.
They have four children.
Eighteen years of marriage and he doesn't want to talk to her.
She took his money and ran away and came here - for what?
You people cannot deliver her. For what? Nothing!
She opened a business - she can't sell. The husband will close it.
Yes, everybody on the father's side - no marriage.
She is the one that said she wants to marry.
She is married for what?
As you can see, the woman is not herself.
She falls to the ground as the evil spirit - the snake -
that destroyed her marriage manifests.
No peace in her marriage. She hates the husband. They are fighting; every day, they are fighting.
From the father's side.
After the confession, T.B. Joshua delivers her in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus, for setting me free!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Angel Nwokoye.
I am originally from Mozambique but I live in South Africa.
I want to thank God that I came to The SCOAN, and I was located on the prayer line on Monday.
I was delivered from the spirit of snake that had been tormenting my marriage.
That spirit used to tell me to leave my marriage.
But I discovered that my husband, after our first child -
I didn't know that he had another child with another woman outside.
Three weeks after, he then told me that there was another woman who had a child for him,
that she came to his shop without the child.
After that, he was drinking, smoking, womanising and gambling.
Whenever I tried to talk to him, there was no peace; we would fight at home
and the children were scattered.
Because of that, I tried to report him to my dad.
My dad said he cannot do anything because I said I wanted to marry a Nigerian,
so I should go ahead and take care of myself.
Both my mother's family and my father's family abandoned me.
There was no one to help.
So now, I thought that I have four children with him.
For two years, he has been living with another lady; he only comes home to change.
He has rented a house for the woman in South Africa, taking care of the lady.
I even tried to confront the lady. The lady said she is not going to leave him
because he is the one who put her into that relationship
so if he wants, he must leave her but she is not leaving.
So now, when he decided that he was leaving, to come to Anambra (Nigeria),
because he is a Nigerian --
When he left, there was a friend of his that was supposed to bring money for him.
What I decided to do after he had left - I took that money,
I bought a ticket to come to The SCOAN.
When I arrived here on Sunday, I thank God that he located me through the prayer line,
and the man of God took care of me; he even gave me 15,000 naira
for my upkeep, food and everything.
So after that, I was delivered and set free.
When I was set free and went to the lodge to sleep,
the snake came to me, asking me what it was that I was doing.
That I now came to The SCOAN to seek for help to be delivered - for what?
When I tried to wake up to see who was talking, the snake vanished.
It vanished; I couldn't see it again.
That is how I realised that I was free and set free indeed.
Man of God, I thank you for what you have done for me.
I am here to seek God's intervention upon my marriage.
I have four kids with him.
Please, Man of God, help me; I have nowhere to go!
I want my husband back but it is not in my hands; I don't want to go to the street with my kids.
We have just heard a wonderful testimony.
In other words, ever since you have been delivered,
you no longer see that snake?
No more - I'm free!
To God be the glory! And you are also here to know God's opinion about your marriage.
Yes.
To God be the glory! What about your husband?
I don't know where he is right now.
Ok, to God be the glory. This was a case that happened last week.
After she was delivered, the man of God took it upon himself
to ask the evangelists to invite her husband.
And to the glory of God, we believe her husband is in the midst of the people here right now.
So we want to invite him forward.
Testimony Time
My name is Ndubuisi Chika Nowokoye.
I am from Oka in Anambra State (Nigeria), residing in South Africa.
This is my junior sister - the last one from my mother's womb.
This woman is my wife.
It is true that she has four kids with me.
I met her seventeen years ago in South Africa.
She is resident in South Africa but originally from Mozambique.
So, when I met her, I approached her like a man approaches a lady.
From there, we entered into a relationship.
But before then, I had broken out from a relationship with a lady who has a kid for me.
When I met her, I approached her; we continued going from there.
She has a family in South Africa.
Her grandfather is living in South Africa; her grandmother is living in South Africa with their children.
So we went and met them.
After that approach to marry her, to which she agreed,
I went to Mozambique to pay marriage rights and everything.
First year to the fourth year, the marriage was so sweet.
Then, I don't know what happened, she wanted to 'ride' me; she wanted to be the man of the house.
She wanted to order me to do what she wanted.
I said, no, I am from Oka.
As far as I am concerned, no woman can put us under this thing.
It is true that I am in South Africa but I know where I come from.
No woman I know can put me in a cage, that whatever she says, is what I will do now.
She wants to know about my money, who I do business with, where I keep the money.
So, many times she would be threatening me that she will take the children and go;
that I will not see the children.
She has done it more than five times.
At a time, it was unbearable.
So, I complained to my sisters and family at home.
They were telling me that I know where I come from;
don't let a woman kill you in South Africa.
If worse comes to worse, let her go.
But I tried to patch up.
It came to a stage where I felt no more happiness in me.
It made me to drink a lot and go out.
Whenever I decided to go back home, my heart would tremble.
I would say, no, let me leave her at home and have my pleasure in the bar.
Six months ago, I had a fatal accident when I was about to go home.
I was drunk, driving home.
My car tumbled eight times; I nearly died.
I came out alive, nothing happened to me, but the car is beyond repair - crushed -
because of this woman.
So at the end of the day, I said to myself, no, for me to die,
I don't want to die for this woman; let me let her go.
I told her that I am travelling to Nigeria to visit my parents but she didn't know my plan.
My plan was that I am fed up.
I don't need her again.
I'm tired of the miserable life we have been living for 12 years now.
So, I came to Nigeria to look for a wife but I did not tell my parents.
I did not tell my father and sisters.
Whenever they are asking of her, I would be saying, she is fine.
When I call her phone, her phone is on voicemail.
Then, I don't know what happened, the whole Saturday I was stressed.
I asked myself, what happened now.
Maybe she has run away again because she ran away with the children many times.
Many times she ran away with my money and misuse it.
The next day being Sunday, I had a call from friends that they saw my wife in The SCOAN.
I said, what?
So does this mean that this woman left a kid of six months with other children for Nigeria?
But if she is in The SCOAN, I don't know, but I want to hear what the man of God will say.
They said that they saw her; she manifested.
I used to watch Emmanuel TV.
I know what the man of God can do.
But now I have decided that I don't want this woman; I don't need her again.
On Monday, I had a call from The SCOAN. They said that the man of God wants to see me.
Hey! That's a call I can't refuse!
If it were her mother, father or brother, I wouldn't come.
But because of this call - it is a call I cannot say no to.
I called my sister that there is a call from The SCOAN,
and that there is nothing I can do; I have to come.
But what I want to tell the man of God - please, I know you get it directly from Heaven,
what is God saying here, but for me, it's okay.
I'm full.
So, I want the man of God to help me, to tell me so that I can continue looking for what I'm looking for.
We thank God for this occasion.
Could you, sir, tell us how many children the woman has for you.
Four.
To God be the glory. And you are here to hear God's opinion from the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua?
Yes, because I know that the man of God hears directly from Heaven.
Whatever he says to me now is what God says.
And that is the final conclusion.
To God be the glory.
As we all know, the man of God, where he is, we believe he is listening to this situation,
and by the special grace of God, he will be coming out in the power of the Holy Ghost
to address this situation.
Let's wait patiently for the man of God's arrival.
Let's hear briefly from your younger sister.
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chinyere Nwokoye.
I'm from Oka (Nigeria).
The man standing beside me is my elder brother.
The lady next to him is his wife Angel.
I've been hearing so many complaints from them.
Almost every week, they called me from South Africa.
If they don't call me, they call my elder sister,
complaining about one thing or the other.
But what I'm going to say is that I believe what is happening in their home is not ordinary.
So I plead with the man of God to also deliver my brother
as he has delivered the wife.
So I'm pleading with the man of God to deliver my brother too
so that peace will reign in their home.
As we have heard it earlier on, the man of God is in the best position
to tell the whole world God's position in this marriage,
and God bless you as you wait patiently to hear from the man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Thank you very much.
I was listening to my brother, and the sister has said it all.
Mr Nwokoye & Family - Nigerian Living In South Africa
The reason why my sister here was misbehaving in the house
was as a result of this evil spirit and she has been delivered.
Now you will have the good of her.
Now you are having a wife.
Now you too need to be delivered.
What marriage now after four children?
It is true you people have married but it is time now to rededicate your marriage.
She is free now from the past.
You too need to be free now from the past.
You know I said challenges - she has a lot of challenges, and God has delivered her.
You too have a lot of challenges, even to the extent that you went outside the marriage to have a child.
And I'm very happy for the honour you give to God.
And I want to tell you that I'm part of your family.
My sister, thank you very much for your intervention.
I want to tell the whole world that this marriage is from God.
After your deliverance, I want to invite you people again back from South Africa.
This is your home, and your home is also my home.
So, I want to tell you that I'm one of your brothers; thank you very much.
She's a wonderful wife; it is just satan, and satan has been removed.
On your own side too, satan needs to be removed
so you people can live in one accord.
DELIVERANCE TIME
Following the words of the man of God,
that the deliverance of the husband will cement the marriage that is from Heaven,
removing the satanic influence and allowing them to live in one accord.
The husband was delivered in the power of the Holy Spirit
when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for him in Jesus' name.
The wife also receives a final touch.
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
And rising to their feet after the deliverance, they thank God and embrace in Jesus' name.
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
People of God, good morning!
My name is Angel Nwokoye.
I am originally from Mozambique but I live in South Africa.
The wonderful man beside me is my lovely husband.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
I'm here to thank God for my deliverance two weeks ago
when I came to The SCOAN.
I came here and had an encounter with the man of God,
and I was delivered from the spirit of snake.
That spirit had really been tormenting me.
It was real because when I was growing up as a child,
I went to my father's village
and that is where my grandmother was telling me the story
that there is a house where that snake lives.
That my great-grandfather was a native doctor,
my grandfather was a native doctor, and my dad was the one
that was supposed to take over but he did not.
So the snake was moving around now, causing my sisters and everybody not to get married,
which was, I think, during that time that the snake entered me but I did not know.
So during that time my husband and I would be fighting; there was no peace.
I discovered that I normally used to see that snake on my pillow;
sometimes I used to see it between my husband and I.
I used to tell him that I used to dream of this big snake
that is coming in between us.
He would say, no problem, this thing will go.
But at the end of the day, I started noticing that this thing now -
I fighting with my husband and thinking that I could correct him - I'm not God.
Then it must have been this snake that is making him to hate me,
and making me to leave the house and misbehave.
So, during that time, I was watching Emmanuel TV,
the man of God was telling us that in relationship and marriage,
you should stay true to God; don't budge, let God release you.
And I would be saying, how will God release me because I was already in pain;
I was undergoing depression. I didn't know who to talk to.
When I called my dad, he would tell me I should take the kids, come home and leave this man.
I would be saying, I know this is not the right thing to do
because where can I go with four kids; they are all his,
and there is nowhere I could go to, so why should my dad be saying this.
To the point when I now talked to my friends, nobody came up with a good advice.
At the end of the day, this thing was known everywhere
that my husband and I were fighting because a particular girl that was fighting with me
from the same church that we were going to.
So now I said, what will I do.
I started watching Emmanuel TV.
I said, God, use these children and remember me for eighteen years of marriage.
Even if I have offended You, forgive me by using these children.
I would take this journey and go to The SCOAN so that I will receive my deliverance.
That was how my husband said he was coming here in December for holidays, and he left the house.
So now when he left, he sent somebody to bring money to us.
I told my son, what will I do with this money because I want to travel to The SCOAN.
My son said, Mummy, even if we don't eat, take this money and go.
Man of God will see you; just believe.
That's what I did. I purchased the ticket without him even knowing that I was coming here.
And I came. When I came here on Sunday,
glory be to God that the man of God located me
and he delivered me from that spirit of snake.
After delivering me, because he is a man of God and hears from Heaven,
he even knew in his spirit that I didn't even have any money, I had nowhere to go to.
He offered me a place to stay, he offered me food,
he took care of me, and I was accommodated. To God be the glory!
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
And then my husband was invited to come over to The SCOAN last week Sunday.
He too was here because he was called to come for reconciliation.
So now, I'm here, Man of God, to thank you.
Thank you very much, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, for the help and the love you gave to me.
I have never been to any church where I was offered accommodation and food for free.
All that you hear is "give"; even if you don't have, they don't want to know.
But God used you to reconcile me with my husband, my family and children.
I want to thank you and thank God Almighty for using you to reconcile me.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
Now, since I have been delivered from that spirit of snake -
on Tuesday when I went back to the lodge to sleep,
the snake tried to come whilst I was sleeping.
It was asking me, "Why are you doing this to me?
Why did you come to The SCOAN for them to deliver you?"
I tried to ask, "Who is that? Who is talking?"
And when I woke up, the snake disappeared; I didn't see it anymore.
Now I am delivered; I am free, in Jesus' name.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
And ever since my deliverance, I can really hug my husband;
we can now talk like husband and wife;
we can now phone our children together, there is peace.
He keeps telling me that he loves me;
that we need to plan how to live together with the children in peace.
There is peace and joy.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ndubuisi Chika Nwokoye.
I am from Oka, Anambra State, Nigeria.
I am very happy to stand before the people of God in this great arena of liberty.
The beautiful lady standing by my side is my lovely wife.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
In June it will be 13 years that we've been married.
At first, it was love.
After five years, it became a war.
Because, you know where I come from, we believe in one thing -
that a woman never rules a man.
And when we go into marriage, we don't go in for love.
We go into marriage - I am an Igbo man - we go into marriage for children.
Even when the woman gives birth to only females and not males, it brings more war.
We don't look at the woman as the first thing.
We look at what she is producing for us because it is like employment.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
If a woman does not give birth to a child, that is another big war.
Another thing is that the woman must be under us - under our authority.
She mustn't have a choice of her own.
She must be obedient, respect us - when we are wrong or right.
Because, as far as I know, in Igbo land, the chief can never be wrong.
If a woman goes out, it is a problem for the woman. But if a man goes out, he is still right
because he can have 2 or 3 wifes, according to the tradition of Igbo land.
But it came to a time - you can be possessed but you won't know that you are possessed.
If someone came to tell me before my deliverance that I was possessed, I would tell the person, "Get out!"
Because everthing I was doing was very right in my view,
never knowing that I was possessed.
This war between my wife and I - it came to a time when I could not take it anymore.
I said to myself, I have gone everywhere; I have gone to so many churches,
deliverance upon deliverance, but this woman is still the same.
I made the decision to take another wife
because in my place, we believe that if you want to quench a fire
of a woman in the house, marry another woman on top of her.
Then the war will leave you and be between her and the other lady that you are bringing in.
So, I told my wife that I was going to Nigeria for holiday, to visit my friends and family
but she didn't know that I was coming to Nigeria to look for a new wife.
As I was searching for this new wife in Nigeria,
I never knew that this woman that I had left in South Africa had landed at The SCOAN.
As I was here in Nigeria, in my hometown Oka, looking around, enjoying myself,
moving about as someone who is celebrating New Year and Christmas together,
looking for a new wife,
all the women I was seeing, I was comparing them with my wife,
I never saw someone as beautiful as her. I wanted to beat her with another beautiful one.
So, as time was going on, it happened on Sunday that I phoned my home in South Africa.
I asked my children, "Where is my wife?" They said that they didn't know her whereabouts.
In the evening I called back again. I asked, "Is she back?" They said, "No".
I asked, "What is happening?"
On Sunday, people started calling me that they saw my wife on Emmanuel TV.
I was shocked because I never knew about it.
I asked, "What happened?"
They said that they saw her.
Okay. I kept quiet.
On Monday, a call came from The SCOAN that they needed to see me here.
They said that the man of God wanted to see me.
That is a call I cannot say no to.
The way I was angry, I even said that I didn't want her forever.
Before I was hiding, then I was telling her openly, "No more!
Although you knew it before but now I'm telling you very openly that I don't want you forever".
She kept quiet; she didn't even answer.
If it were before, when I said something, she would answer with fire.
Okay. If it were the mother that called me, she knows I would not come.
Or her father or any of her relations.
But this was a call that touched my life.
The man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, is someone that
when I watch him on Emmanuel TV, my body is shaking.
So I couldn't say no.
I took my car, called my friends and said, "I'm going to The SCOAN on Saturday
because a call came from here that they needed me".
When I came here, I didn't want to see my wife's face.
I was so angry because in my mind I said,
"Whatever happens, I have taken the decision - I need a new wife".
So, I said, "Man of God, whatever you say, I will accept it because I know that you hear directly from God".
The man of God told me that this marriage is from God.
That calmed me down - number 1.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
Number 2 - that same Sunday evening, I went to the prayer line
where the man of God is delivering people.
When I was coming, I was myself.
Arriving there, immediately the man of God raised his hand,
I went back; I don't know what happened to me.
I fell under the anointing.
I said to myself, "Ah, am I myself?"
I wanted to stand up but there was no strength. I fell back again.
My head was as if it was divided into two.
This side is talking one thing; the other side is talking another thing.
So, I couldn't get myself very well.
After the deliverance, when I went to the place
where the man of God gave us to stay for free,
I told my wife, "Still now, I don't know what is happening to me!
My head is still divided. This one this side; this one talking another thing but I will see".
Then I fell asleep.
When I woke up in the morning, I looked at my wife.
She looked so young and beautiful.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
I said to myself, ""Wow! Is it a mistake that I should make?"
So this girl I came to look for in Nigeria is still the same one I left in South Africa
that came here beautiful like this.
I said to myself, "Now I know that I really need deliverance; I am possessed".
Because so many things I was doing before,
I see it was wrong - wrong after wrong.
I asked myself, "Was it me doing this?" I was shocked.
I said to my wife, "Please forgive me!
Whatever wrong I have done to you before, forgive me!
I was not using my real eye. I had eyes then but I could not see.
Now that I can see clearly, you are beautiful!"
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
From that day, every day she is looking new,
more than new, more than beautiful.
I said, "Ay!" Today I stand in this great arena to ask the people of God
to thank the man of God, Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, for me.
He really reconciled my wife and I.
I am very happy and I promise that I will love her more and more.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
My advice to people, married people, all over the world
that are having a similar problem to what I encountered before
is that never say no when you enter into marriage.
Think of the heart that you wanted to break.
It is really not your heart but someone's that came from her parents' house to be with you.
Remember what God said that the woman will leave her mother and father,
join with a man and they will become one.
Whatever you encounter, never say no.
If it is so much for you that you cannot carry,
know that there is a place - the arena of liberty - where your problem can be solved.
Try, make your way to The SCOAN1
When you arrive here, I know that the God of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua
that visited me and delivered me will surely do it for you.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Deliverance / Reconciliation Testimony
My advice to the whole world and to married couples is that
we should always seek the face of God.
I know women would be saying that I don't know what I'm talking about.
But I went through so many pains; I've been there; I have done that.
Please, don't ever feel like leaving your home.
Just stay strong and help your husband. He might not know what he is doing
Be it you are a man and it is your wife that is misbehaving.
Be strong and believe in God.
Tell yourself that you will come together and find a solution.
And the advice I give is that the arena of liberty - The SCOAN -
whatever it will cost you, just land here and God will see you through.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
People of God, Emmanuel! (God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Angel Nwokoye.
The man standing beside me is my husband, Mr Chika Ndubuisi Nwokoye.
We are here by the grace of God to testify for what God did in our lives,
concerning the reconciliation when I came to The SCOAN on January 15th.
I want to thank God because today, there is peace through the reconciliation;
there is peace and love between my husband and I.
Our children are happy, we are living happily
and I thank God and I thank Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua for allowing God to use him
to reconcile this marriage.
The situation was really terrible
but I thank God that I've been delivered
and now I'm fully happy in my marriage.
My name is Mr Ndubuisi Chika Nwokoye.
I'm from Oka, the capital of Anambra State, Nigeria.
The woman standing beside me is my lovely wife, Angel Nwokoye.
People of God, this is something I don't know how to explain.
It is something that is wonderful; something I have tried by all means to use my power.
I prayed to the Lord, fasted a lot but nothing worked. I became frustrated.
That is why I began to hate my wife the more
because when things were happening, I thought I could correct one or two,
but nothing was happening.
When I came here in January, I was invited by Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I came here - it was wonderful.
That touch of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua changed everything in my life;
changed everything in my family;
changed everything that I thought could not be done.
You know before, I didn't know my children much.
I always liked to stay out at night.
At day time, I would not come in.
Night time - that is when I loved to go out.
I spent my time in the bar, with friends and doing all sorts of rubbish,
not knowing that the real joy is my family.
That the real joy is to stay, to know my children and my wife.
After the touch of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua - wow!
It was something that I cannot explain.
I began to enjoy staying at home, studying my children and staying with my wife.
In fact, I was in marriage but I was not in love before.
But now, I have come back with love; my marriage has become sweet.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus Christ!
My life became sweet.
My marriage became sweet.
My children, everything around me became sweet.
In fact, another thing - poverty that was following me disappeared.
Before, it was hand to mouth.
All the things I was bragging about was just a brag because no man paid.
But after the touch of Senior Prophet T.B. Joshua, wonders started happening.
My father, Chika Nwokoye, 90 years old, passed away.
But you know in Igbo land, to bury someone is not an easy something.
Espcially an old man - a celebration of life.
But when I looked around, what God had given me after I visited The SCOAN,
I smiled because I was loaded.
Wow! To God be the glory!
I can see that our brother is full of joy.
My advice to people is that every man that is in marriage,
please know it that marriage is of God.
If you encounter what I have encountered, don't chase your wife away.
Don't go and take another wife.
Consult God and you will see that God is in The SCOAN.
God will do the same thing in your life that he has done for me.
I'm so grateful; I'm so happy.
Put your hands together beautifully for Jesus!
Wow! To God be the glory! We thank God Almighty, and we also want to advise you
and encourage you as you rightly said, don't run from God but rather run to God
because He is the answer to all fundamental issues of life.
Never a problem he cannot solve
because He has given that spirit of reconciliation to reconcile families,
to reconcile nations and to reconcile the whole world.
Mr & Mrs Nwokoye - Reconciliation / Deliverance Testimony